// creating an array and passing the number, questions, options, and answers
let questions = [
    {
    numb: 1,
    question: "What is the name of the smart bear in this story?",
    answer: "Berry the smart bear",
    options: [
      "Bruno the smart bear",
      "Brandon the smart bear",
      "Berry the smart bear",
      "Bradely the smart bear"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 2,
    question: "What did Berry do after he woke up feeling hungry?",
    answer: "He got up and sterted searching for food",
    options: [
      "He went back to sleep crying",
      "He called out for his mother for food",
      "He got up and just spent the morning rolling on the grasses",
      "He got up and sterted searching for food"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 3,
    question: "What is the sound Berry heard when serching around?",
    answer: "The buzzing sound of bees",
    options: [
      "Sound of water at the river",
      "Sound of people talking",
      "The buzzing sound of bees",
      "Sound of dogs barking"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 4,
    question: "How did he find the buzzing bees?",
    answer: "He followed the direction of the buzzing sound",
    options: [
      "The bees found him instead",
      "He just moved around untill he found them",
      "He was just lucky and found them",
      "He followed the direction of the buzzing sound"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 5,
    question: "What do bees make in their hives?",
    answer: "They make honey",
    options: [
      "They make slime",
      "They make sap",
      "They make sugar",
      "They make honey"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 6,
    question: "What do we call a group of bees livivng together?",
    answer: "A colony",
    options: [
      "A heard",
      "A crew",
      "A colony",
      "A community"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 7,
    question: "The type of bees in a colony?",
    answer: "Queen bee, Drone bees, and Worker bees",
    options: [
      "King bee, Drone bees, and Worker bees",
      "Queen bee, Drone bees, and Worker bees",
      "Queen bee, Fly bees, and Busy bees",
      "King bee, Fly bees, and Busy bees"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 8,
    question: "The honey was high up, how did berry get it?",
    answer: "He used a branch with leaves to reach it",
    options: [
      "He waited untill the honey started driping down to his mouth",
      "He climbed up to the tree",
      "He used his arm to reach it",
      "He used a branch with leaves to reach it"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 9,
    question: "Why did berry want the honey so bad?",
    answer: "He was hungry and honey is very delicious with a lot of nutrients",
    options: [
      "He was bored and wanted to play with the bees",
      "He was hungry and honey is very delicious with a lot of nutrients",
      "He just wanted to see what will happen",
      "He was curious"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 10,
    question: "What do we learn from Berry's story?",
    answer: "We can use what we have to get what we need",
    options: [
      "We should be lazy to think",
      "We should cry for help all the time",
      "We can use what we have to get what we need",
      "We can not get what we need"
    ]
  },
  // you can uncomment the below codes and make duplicate as more as you want to add question
  // but remember you need to give the numb value serialize like 1,2,3,5,6,7,8,9.....
  //   {
  //   numb: 6,
  //   question: "Your Question is Here",
  //   answer: "Correct answer of the question is here",
  //   options: [
  //     "Option 1",
  //     "option 2",
  //     "option 3",
  //     "option 4"
  //   ]
  // },
];
